[Applause]
H and how is the shift towards motor
likely to happen? Is it going to impact
your portfolio profitability, claims
ratios? What's the outlook on motor is
what I'd want to really understand
because there's such a push with regard
to auto growth.
>> In the recent months, we do see
incremental opportunities playing out
also in the context of commercial
vehicles and therefore to that extent
possibly you see you may see a mix which
can undergo a change. So that's
something that we keep balancing every
month in terms of uh which are the
segments that we need to underwrite
which are the segments that we need to
be slightly more guarded and therefore
the outcome is what we kind of exhibit
to the market. Uh to your final point
and how do we see the trend play out for
motor going ahead uh this has to be
looked at in couple of context one if
you look at for motor industry combined
ratios it is currently elevated at 125%.
This is the industry numbers. Uh
industry combined ratios for motor is at
125%. And therefore to that extent it
effectively means that you're losing 25
pes for every rupee of premium that
you're underwriting. So that's a lot of
money for the market to lose that. And
therefore to that extent you have to be
slightly more guarded in terms of what
kind of quality of risk that you want to
underwrite. Which is why we have been
very very selective on the quality of
the book that one wants to write in the
context of motor. But within that I
think we are seeing a lot of uh green
shoots particularly with the state of
reforms that the various regulatory
authorities have been able to put on
ground and that is kind of occurring
very well in the context of ICL robot.
But in terms of how does one see the
growth play out very very positive is
the way we kind of look at in terms of
how things will play out. So that is one
factor in terms of the combined issues
for the industry. The second factor is
this is the third year of the glide path
for expense of management guidelines. So
companies which have been in exance of
the limits on expense of management has
to bring down the uh bring down their uh
expenses of management. For SS alumbard
we have always been well within the
limits and therefore that will also be a
key factor uh that one would look at
very very closely in terms of how growth
in motor is likely to shape up for going
ahead.